<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: about-site | Zombie Muva-Fukka, Muva-Fukka]]></title>
  <link href="http://zmfmf.com/blog/categories/about-site/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://zmfmf.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-08-08T19:42:32+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://zmfmf.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Rizla Khan]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fingers And Questions]]></title>
    <link href="http://zmfmf.com/blog/2013/08/08/fingers-and-questions/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-08T11:46:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://zmfmf.com/blog/2013/08/08/fingers-and-questions</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m still undecided on what to write here.  Non-fiction seems most likely but I would hate to be writing a diary so I&rsquo;ll try very hard to leave out written opinion and myself.  Still, a diary of sorts will be formed as the choices of what to include here will be dictated by my opinion and over time as my mind changes so then will the content.  I&rsquo;ll live with that.</p>

<p>Fiction will be tagged and I&rsquo;ll find some way to place it within a border so as to contain it and it&rsquo;s limitless domain.</p>

<p>The reason for this blog is to help me become a better writer.  That is all and I&rsquo;m publicly displaying my journey for motivational reasons in order to help with my goal.  Firstly I will only publish finished posts and secondly I want to avoid as much shame as I can.  The way to becoming a good writer is to write and the quantity of posts on this blog will be an easy measure of my dedication to the task.  If I feel less shame in the future then I&rsquo;ve either improved in the craft or not improved and wallow with a smile in mud.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn me on]]></title>
    <link href="http://zmfmf.com/blog/2013/08/03/turn-me-on/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-03T12:57:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://zmfmf.com/blog/2013/08/03/turn-me-on</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Blog is online.  My window is open but I don&rsquo;t hear any shouts.
Is it possible to successfully blog about nothing happening?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
